<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>GQ — Profiles</title><link>https://www.gq.com/about/profiles</link><description>Fresh profiles from GQ</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 07:40:17 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>BigXthaPlug Is Bigger Than Texas</title><link>https://www.gq.com/story/bigxthaplug-gq-hype</link><description>BigXthaPlug put Texas rap back on the map. Now, on the heels of a hypnotic album packed with hits, he’s plotting to take his Lone Star appeal worldwide.</description><category>Culture</category><enclosure url="https://media.gq.com/photos/67f3f7a1606fdb9fabcc0e2d/4:3/w_1024%2Cc_limit/GQ0425_BigX_02_DIG.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 07:40:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Can Kat Abughazaleh Help Democrats Grow a Spine?</title><link>https://www.gq.com/story/kat-abughazaleh-congress</link><description>She’s a lefty 26-year-old internet star. Her primary opponent is 80 and has held office since 1999. Inside a race for Congress that could help revive a doddering Democratic Party.</description><category>Culture</category><enclosure url="https://media.gq.com/photos/67fd7efaffd40fb444f0ea29/4:3/w_1024%2Cc_limit/0%2520lede_Z1A1357-positive-Edit.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 07:40:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Young Thug Speaks About His New Album and Life After Jail</title><link>https://www.gq.com/story/young-thug-speaks-about-his-new-album-uy-scuti-and-life-after-jail</link><description>The Atlanta rapper reveals new details about his two and a half years of detention and his latest album,UY Scuti, in an exclusive interview and GQ Video Cover Story.</description><category>Culture</category><enclosure url="https://media.gq.com/photos/680babfed3355d0ecd6df269/4:3/w_1024%2Cc_limit/GQ_GQO_11_077_DIGITAL_COVER_VIDEO_YOUNG_THUG_042425_TEXTED_h264_V2.00_01_58_06.Still005.png" length="0" type="image/jpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 07:40:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Lewis Pullman Steps Out of the Shadows</title><link>https://www.gq.com/story/lewis-pullman-steps-out-of-the-shadows</link><description>With his breakthrough performance inThunderbolts*as the MCU’s newest all-powerful hero (and its creepiest new villain), the actor has fans and the film biz asking, “What about Bob?”</description><category>Culture</category><enclosure url="https://media.gq.com/photos/681a7f368025b9625baeea5c/4:3/w_1024%2Cc_limit/002_LPxGQ_FINAL.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 07:40:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>HowOvercompensatingStar Benito Skinner Created the Sitcom of the Summer</title><link>https://www.gq.com/story/benito-skinner-overcompensating-cast-profile</link><description>His new series about a closeted jock, has a hilarious ensemble cast—composed of Wally Baram, Mary Beth Barone, Rish Shah, and more—plus a coming-of-age story like you’ve never seen before.GQwent inside the Benny Drama universe as he makes the leap from your Instagram feed to your TV.</description><category>Culture</category><enclosure url="https://media.gq.com/photos/681b9ca1e8801d74ef10612d/4:3/w_1024%2Cc_limit/001-cast-000199640035%2520copy.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 07:40:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Adam Duritz Is Just Happy to Be Anywhere</title><link>https://www.gq.com/story/adam-duritz-is-just-happy-to-be-anywhere</link><description>A soulfully earnest singer whose folk-rock band stormed the charts in the age of grunge and irony, the Counting Crows frontman became both an overnight icon and an easy target—and throughout his band’s rise and fall, he kept quiet about his struggle with mental illness. At 60, he’s found some peace at last. Now what?</description><category>Culture</category><enclosure url="https://media.gq.com/photos/681d027d0b6d3b8c15aa9ac0/4:3/w_1024%2Cc_limit/2021-024_G_0044_R1%2520copy%25202.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 07:40:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Jon Hamm Gets Back in the Driver’s Seat</title><link>https://www.gq.com/story/jon-hamm-gq-hype</link><description>After shaking off the ghost of Don Draper by playing a parade of bad guys, goofball guest stars, and even Tom Cruise’s boss, the 53-year-old actor said yes toYour Friends &amp; Neighbors,his first TV-series lead in a decade—and found out people still want to watch Jon Hamm play a morally complex rich guy with a secret.</description><category>Culture</category><enclosure url="https://media.gq.com/photos/682b7bc9183df7c5fb37d757/4:3/w_1024%2Cc_limit/site%2520social-_GQ_JON_HAMM_MM_%25203.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 07:40:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>The Last of UsStar Kaitlyn Dever Is Only Getting Stronger</title><link>https://www.gq.com/story/kaitlyn-dever-gq-hype</link><description>In making the zombie show’s most harrowing scene yet, Kaitlyn Dever’s life and work collided devastatingly. But in the end it helped her process the worst period of her life.</description><category>Culture</category><enclosure url="https://media.gq.com/photos/682df4c50865018e5b3a58ac/4:3/w_1024%2Cc_limit/May%252026%2520-%2520Kaitlyn%2520Dever_Online_Header.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 07:40:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Adam Friedland Could Be the Millennial Jon Stewart. But Does He Want That?</title><link>https://www.gq.com/story/adam-friedland</link><description>The 38-year-old comedian started his YouTube seriesThe Adam Friedland Showmostly as a joke. But in the wake of an election that podcasters helped swing in Donald Trump’s favor, he’s fielding interview offers from politicians desperate to connect with disaffected young voters any way they can—even if it means getting trolled on camera by the former co-host of a podcast calledCum Town.</description><category>Culture</category><enclosure url="https://media.gq.com/photos/6835d27154e8452370fb37c5/4:3/w_1024%2Cc_limit/0-%2520site%2520and%2520social%2520GQ_AdamFriedland0184.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 07:40:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>How Haim Quit Caring About All That</title><link>https://www.gq.com/story/haim-gq-hype</link><description>With their fourth album,I Quit, Alana, Danielle, and Este Haim expunge negative feelings about shitty exes, bad dates, and a rock music community that refuses to acknowledge them. Now, as Alana puts it during a hang in the Valley, “it’s time to party.”</description><category>Culture</category><enclosure url="https://media.gq.com/photos/683da3110f5c6e1fda7d5f6f/4:3/w_1024%2Cc_limit/GQ_SUMMER_ONLINE_HAIM_HEADER.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 07:40:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Jacques Marie Mage: The Sunglasses That Are Changing the Face of Pop Culture</title><link>https://www.gq.com/story/jacques-marie-mage-the-sunglasses-that-are-changing-the-face-of-pop-culture</link><description>How eccentric French designer Jérôme Mage transformed his LA brand, Jacques Marie Mage, into the most coveted and cultish name in sunglasses—and created the go-to shades for the celebrity class.</description><category>Style</category><enclosure url="https://media.gq.com/photos/683f180563ec0e89d275ba40/4:3/w_1024%2Cc_limit/GQ0725_JacquesMarieMage_01.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 07:40:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>How Teyana Taylor Battled the Competition in Two Industries—And Won</title><link>https://www.gq.com/story/teyana-taylor-gq-hype</link><description>Five years ago, she walked away from her record deal and bet on herself as an actress. Now she’s dropping a wild new visual album,Escape Room—and starring in Paul Thomas Anderson’s hotly anticipatedOne Battle After Another.</description><category>Culture</category><enclosure url="https://media.gq.com/photos/6847534fe58f20b644e1ae91/4:3/w_1024%2Cc_limit/site-social-000510990010_01_RGB.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 07:40:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Billionaires Love His Sweaters. They Love His Ideas Even More</title><link>https://www.gq.com/story/brunello-cucinelli-profile-2025</link><description>Since 1978, Brunello Cucinelli has sought to lead his luxury empire—and the town that became its heart—with benevolence. And with the industry bracing for tariffs and trade wars, protecting his self-made Umbrian paradise has never felt more vital.</description><category>Style</category><enclosure url="https://media.gq.com/photos/68508c0121681e88c148d572/4:3/w_1024%2Cc_limit/GQ_SUMMER_Brunello_Online3.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 07:40:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>We're All Aboard the Morgan Spector Train</title><link>https://www.gq.com/story/morgan-spector-gq-hype</link><description>TheGilded Ageactor is back as robber baron George Russell (affectionately known as “Railroad Daddy” to his fans). Ahead of the HBO period drama’s thrilling third season, we hung out with Spector on the Upper East Side to talk subversive masculinity, being a wife guy, and suddenly becoming famous in his 40s.</description><category>Culture</category><enclosure url="https://media.gq.com/photos/68503411059bbaa78f8ac671/4:3/w_1024%2Cc_limit/site%2520social%2520GQ0925_HypeSpector_D_09.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 07:40:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Can David Corenswet Save Superman?</title><link>https://www.gq.com/story/david-corenswet-gq-hype</link><description>In a world-historical moment rife with villainy and loose scruples, James Gunn has staked his reboot of the DC Comics Universe on a Superman with core values, a sunny disposition, and a weakness for romance. Says Corenswet, who has to make it all work: “A role like Superman seems like something that everybody would want, and that’s not true.”</description><category>Culture</category><enclosure url="https://media.gq.com/photos/68507373230c38ab71627e24/4:3/w_1024%2Cc_limit/GQ0925_HypeCorenswet_D_01_SITE.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 07:40:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>HowToo MuchStar Will Sharpe Reinvented the Rom-Com Heartthrob</title><link>https://www.gq.com/story/will-sharpe-gq-hype</link><description>In Lena Dunham’s buzzy new Netflix series, the actor spins the love interest into something much more idiosyncratic—emotional baggage and all.</description><category>Culture</category><enclosure url="https://media.gq.com/photos/6877c9a7b963d8b9e9928a2a/4:3/w_1024%2Cc_limit/July%252021%2520-%2520Will%2520Sharpe_Online_Header.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 07:40:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>How Tyler Childers Made the Most Visionary Country Album of the Year</title><link>https://www.gq.com/story/tyler-childers-snipe-hunter-profile</link><description>He’s an arena-filling Nashville outsider who wrote a Black Lives Matter anthem and put a gay love story in a music video. Now, fresh off a pilgrimage to India, he's releasing his spiritual and artistic opus,Snipe Hunter. “If I’m trying to talk to another young Tyler out there, he needs to know he's not going to hell for thinking something else different.”</description><category>Culture</category><enclosure url="https://media.gq.com/photos/6880f3a168b5715d2f6177a8/4:3/w_1024%2Cc_limit/st%2520sc%2520Tyler_Childers_Nashville_Finals-7.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 07:40:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Wednesday’s Plan to Keep Southern Rock Weird</title><link>https://www.gq.com/story/wednesday-bleeds-karly-hartzman</link><description>The frontman of the Drive-By Truckers says she leads one of the greatest live rock acts of all time. Mannequin Pussy’s singer compares her to “a goth Dolly Parton.” But as the hype builds, Wednesday singer-songwriter Karly Hartzman is determined not to become the next “prince of Brooklyn.” “Just being a little outside of the norm,” she says, “is such a beautiful weapon.”</description><category>Culture</category><enclosure url="https://media.gq.com/photos/68d9d8e0849850c8cd87e6d1/4:3/w_1024%2Cc_limit/EricRyanAnderson_Wednesday_013.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 07:40:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Marine Turned Oysterman Graham Platner Is Ready to Fight Trump. Will MAGA Men Join Him?</title><link>https://www.gq.com/story/graham-platner-maine-senate</link><description>In the battle for the soul of the Democratic Party, Senate candidate Graham Platner might be the perfect soldier: The virile, earthy working man many male politicians wish they were, with the committed lefty beliefs many voters are now demanding. But here in Maine, he’ll need to win over some Trump voters—if he can even make it through the primary.</description><category>Culture</category><enclosure url="https://media.gq.com/photos/68e56418857df2a638646986/4:3/w_1024%2Cc_limit/DSCF0649_SITE.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 07:40:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>How Josh O’Connor Became the Thinking Man’s Leading Man</title><link>https://www.gq.com/story/gq-hype-josh-oconnor-2025</link><description>ChallengersandThe Crownmade him the internet’s most reluctant thirst trap. Now, with no less than four new films (including the nextKnives Out), the actor stands on the precipice of megastardom. But, as he explains on an idyllic stroll (and dip) at his rural retreat, he’s determined to stay true to himself.</description><category>Culture</category><enclosure url="https://media.gq.com/photos/68e7b70e4a7e82877b613f2b/4:3/w_1024%2Cc_limit/GQ_NOV_ONLINE_JOC_HEADER.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 07:40:17 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>