<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>The New Yorker — Reporting</title><link>https://www.newyorker.com/magazine/reporting</link><description>Latest reporting from The New Yorker</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 05:44:27 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>Who My Child Was and Would Be</title><link>https://www.newyorker.com/magazine/2025/11/10/who-my-child-was-and-would-be</link><description>When Nat transitioned, I learned that when someone you love changes, you change, too.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 05:44:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>The Runaway Monkeys Upending the Animal-Rights Movement</title><link>https://www.newyorker.com/magazine/2025/11/10/the-runaway-monkeys-upending-the-animal-rights-movement</link><description>A troop of macaques escaped one of the largest primate-breeding facilities in America. Now a strange coalition of uncompromising activists andMAGAloyalists is demanding that all lab animals be set free.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 05:44:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Joachim Trier Has Put Oslo on the Cinematic Map</title><link>https://www.newyorker.com/magazine/2025/11/10/joachim-trier-profile</link><description>His new film, “Sentimental Value,” is another intimate character study set in the Norwegian capital. His approach to directing is as empathic as his films.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 05:44:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Hannah Goldfield on Anthony Bourdain’s “Don’t Eat Before Reading This”</title><link>https://www.newyorker.com/magazine/takes/hannah-goldfield-on-anthony-bourdains-dont-eat-before-reading-this</link><description>Bourdain was much more than a whistle-blower, even at the very beginning of what would become his second, incredibly significant career.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 05:44:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>David Byrne’s Career of Earnest Alienation</title><link>https://www.newyorker.com/magazine/2025/11/17/david-byrne-profile</link><description>At seventy-three, the former front man of Talking Heads is still asking questions about what it means to be alive. But now he’s also offering ideas of hopefulness and service.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 05:44:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>What Was the American Revolution For?</title><link>https://www.newyorker.com/magazine/2025/11/17/what-was-the-american-revolution-for</link><description>Amid plans to mark the nation’s semiquincentennial, many are asking whether or not the people really do rule, and whether the law is still king.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 05:44:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Rian Johnson Is an Agatha Christie for the Netflix Age</title><link>https://www.newyorker.com/magazine/2025/11/17/rian-johnson-is-an-agatha-christie-for-the-netflix-age</link><description>The director revived the cozy mystery with “Knives Out.” In a new sequel, can he find his way to the end of the maze?</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 05:44:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Laura Loomer’s Endless Payback</title><link>https://www.newyorker.com/magazine/2025/11/17/laura-loomers-endless-payback</link><description>The President’s self-appointed loyalty enforcer inspires fear and vexation across Washington. What’s behind her vetting crusades?</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 05:44:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>The Strange Afterlife of Hilma af Klint, Painting’s Posthumous Star</title><link>https://www.newyorker.com/magazine/2025/11/24/the-strange-afterlife-of-hilma-af-klint-paintings-posthumous-star</link><description>As af Klint’s fame has grown, so have the questions—about what she believed, whom she worked with, and who should be allowed to speak in her name.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 05:44:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Hanif Abdurraqib on Ellen Willis’s Review of Elvis in Las Vegas</title><link>https://www.newyorker.com/magazine/takes/hanif-abdurraqib-on-ellen-willis-elvis-review</link><description>The magazine’s first pop-music critic was never afraid to be overtaken by unexpected delight, even if it came at the expense of some preëxisting skepticism.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 05:44:27 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>