<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>NYT — Magazine</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/international/section/magazine</link><description>Latest stories from NYT Magazine</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 14 Sep 2025 19:15:31 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>How Has Being Perpetually Single Affected You?</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2025/09/05/magazine/forever-single-relationships-love-submissions.html</link><description>We want to hear from women over the age of 30 who feel as if they have not yet had a meaningful relationship for a New York Times Magazine feature.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Brené Brown Doesn’t Want to Be Your Self-Help Guru Anymore</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2025/09/06/magazine/brene-brown-interview.html</link><description>The author and podcaster wants to apply her old ideas about vulnerability and empathy to the workplace.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>I’ve Prepped for Future Disasters. Do I Have to Help Those Who Didn’t?</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2025/09/06/magazine/disaster-prep-sharing-ethics.html</link><description>We can’t be the emergency food bank for everyone, but could we really let others suffer?</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>What We Know About JPMorgan’s Long Relationship With Jeffrey Epstein</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2025/09/08/magazine/what-we-know-about-jpmorgans-long-relationship-with-jeffrey-epstein.html</link><description>Times reporters combed through thousands of pages of legal and financial records to understand how America’s leading lender enabled the notorious sexual predator.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>The Best Part of Any Piece of Mail Is the Stamp</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2025/09/09/magazine/the-best-part-of-any-piece-of-mail-is-the-stamp.html</link><description>These tiny rectangles hold memory and mystery, and they will travel where you will not.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>A Jane Austen-Inspired Roast Chicken That’s Remarkably Well Done</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2025/09/10/magazine/roast-chicken-grapes-recipe.html</link><description>A pairing of grapes and red onions makes a classic recipe feel especially current.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>An Essay Contest Winner Used A.I. Should She Return the $1,000 Award?</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2025/09/10/magazine/essay-contest-ai-ethics.html</link><description>What happened should be taken as a wake-up call, rather than a crime scene.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>What Happened to Cameron Crowe? He Has Answers.</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2025/09/13/magazine/cameron-crowe-interview.html</link><description>The writer-director made hit after hit movie, until he didn’t. But he doesn’t let it get him down.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Sep 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>How the Trump Administration Is Dismantling America’s Cancer-Research System</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2025/09/14/magazine/trump-administration-cancer.html</link><description>Here are the takeaways from The New York Times Times Magazine article on how the cancer-research system, which has helped save millions of lives, is under threat in one of its most productive moments.</description><pubDate>Sun, 14 Sep 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>My Brother-in-Law Can’t Care for Himself. Do His Siblings Have to Bail Him Out?</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2025/09/13/magazine/brother-cant-care-for-himself-siblings-bail-him-out-ethics.html</link><description>He rarely communicates with the family, except when he’s in trouble.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Sep 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>The Cost of Performing Childhood for Your Parent’s Art</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2025/09/12/magazine/child-subjects-art-abuse-sally-mann-molly-jong-fast-ruby-franke.html</link><description>It’s not quite #MeToo, but a spate of new memoirs is forcing a reckoning on what consent means when your parent is the artist.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Trump Is Shutting Down the War On Cancer</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2025/09/14/magazine/cancer-research-grants-funds-trump.html</link><description>America’s cancer research system, which has helped save millions of lives, is under threat in one of its most productive moments.</description><pubDate>Sun, 14 Sep 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>When Dementia Steals the Imagination of a Children’s Book Writer</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2025/09/14/magazine/robert-munsch-author-children-books-dementia.html</link><description>Robert Munsch wrote “The Paper Bag Princess,” “Love You Forever” and other classics by performing them over and over for kids. But dementia is now stealing his imagination.</description><pubDate>Sun, 14 Sep 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>