<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>NYT — Magazine</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/international/section/magazine</link><description>Latest stories from NYT Magazine</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 22:40:42 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>What Disturbing Art Can Teach Us About Our Own Shame and Fear</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2025/09/23/magazine/art-stutter.html</link><description>I found myself drawn to 18th-century sculptures. When I see them, I see myself — a stutterer.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>This Easy Side Does Double Duty at Dinner</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2025/09/24/magazine/parsnips-roast-side-dish.html</link><description>Parsnips dressed in miso and lemon, then topped with arugula and Parmesan can be a glorious accompaniment — or the whole meal.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>‘To Catch a Predator’ Ended Almost 20 Years Ago. Its Grim Legacy Lives on.</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2025/09/24/magazine/to-catch-a-predator-reality-tv.html</link><description>The flippant humiliation that once coursed through the reality-TV landscape has found a more dynamic environment online, where our hunger for schadenfreude can run wild.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>The Filmmaker Who Finds the Humanity in History’s ‘Monsters’</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2025/09/25/magazine/joshua-oppenheimer-films-director-profile.html</link><description>Joshua Oppenheimer’s films show the political value of empathy in our polarized age.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Can You Use Your Spouse as a Hand Towel?</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/interactive/2025/09/27/magazine/hand-drying-hodgman-quiz.html</link><description>A ruling on a home hygiene dispute.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Sean Penn Let Himself Get Away With Things for 15 Years. Not Anymore.</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2025/09/27/magazine/sean-penn-interview.html</link><description>The actor and instigator is ready for his renaissance.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>I’m Concerned About Sweatshops. Should It Change What I Buy?</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2025/09/27/magazine/magazine-email/sweatshops-clothing-ethics.html</link><description>How to balance a concern for human rights with concern for those who depend on jobs in overseas factories?</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>What the Public Memory of Charlie Kirk Revealed</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2025/09/28/magazine/charlie-kirk-rhetoric.html</link><description>For those who felt denigrated by his rhetoric, the bipartisan tributes to him as a champion of free speech augured something dangerous: the mainstreaming of formerly extremist views.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Want to Know What Men Are Thinking? Go Get a Haircut.</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2025/09/30/magazine/barbershops-masculinity-men-culture.html</link><description>The version of masculinity you might see getting your hair cut is more complex than the caricature presented in the manosphere.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Five Takeaways About the Culture of Lawlessness in the U.S. Special Forces</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2025/09/30/magazine/afghanistan-war-green-berets-trump-hegseth.html</link><description>Until now, many of the troubling events that took place during the war in Afghanistan have been shrouded in secrecy.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>The L.A. Dodgers Risk Alienating Their Fans or Angering Trump</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2025/10/01/magazine/los-angeles-dodgers-trump-latinos.html</link><description>For decades, the Dodgers have been the pride of L.A.’s Latino community. Trump’s immigration raids are testing that.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Is It OK to Talk to My Daughter About Her Weight?</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2025/10/01/magazine/magazine-email/talk-to-daughter-about-weight-ethics.html</link><description>She may be headed for a serious problem. How can we raise this with her without pushing her away?</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Why Jane Goodall Still Has Hope for Us Humans</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/interactive/2021/07/12/magazine/jane-goodall-interview.html</link><description>“Traveling the world I’d see so many projects of restoration, people tackling what seemed impossible and not giving up.”</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Nine Bodies Turned Up at a Green Beret Outpost. What Really Happened?</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2025/09/30/magazine/2012-green-beret-killings-nerkh-war-crimes.html</link><description>In 2012, after a team member was nearly killed, a Special Forces unit went on a rampage that might have been one of the worst war crimes in recent U.S. history.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>