<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>NYT — Magazine</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/international/section/magazine</link><description>Latest stories from NYT Magazine</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 14:47:01 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>Brené Brown Doesn’t Want to Be Your Self-Help Guru Anymore</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2025/09/06/magazine/brene-brown-interview.html</link><description>The author and podcaster wants to apply her old ideas about vulnerability and empathy to the workplace.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>I’ve Prepped for Future Disasters. Do I Have to Help Those Who Didn’t?</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2025/09/06/magazine/disaster-prep-sharing-ethics.html</link><description>We can’t be the emergency food bank for everyone, but could we really let others suffer?</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>How JPMorgan Enabled the Crimes of Jeffrey Epstein</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2025/09/08/magazine/jeffrey-epstein-jp-morgan.html</link><description>A Times investigation found that America’s leading bank spent years supporting — and profiting from — the notorious sex offender, ignoring red flags, suspicious activity and concerned executives.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>What We Know About JPMorgan’s Long Relationship With Jeffrey Epstein</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2025/09/08/magazine/what-we-know-about-jpmorgans-long-relationship-with-jeffrey-epstein.html</link><description>Times reporters combed through thousands of pages of legal and financial records to understand how America’s leading lender enabled the notorious sexual predator.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>The Best Part of Any Piece of Mail Is the Stamp</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2025/09/09/magazine/the-best-part-of-any-piece-of-mail-is-the-stamp.html</link><description>These tiny rectangles hold memory and mystery, and they will travel where you will not.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>A Jane Austen-Inspired Roast Chicken That’s Remarkably Well Done</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2025/09/10/magazine/roast-chicken-grapes-recipe.html</link><description>A pairing of grapes and red onions makes a classic recipe feel especially current.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Guitar Nerds and Surf Bros Didn’t Want to ‘Get Political.’ Then Came the Tariffs.</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2025/09/10/magazine/trump-tariffs-youtube-politics.html</link><description>In the online niches where people discuss guitars, surfing, makeup and countless other interests, ideology is becoming harder to quarantine.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>An Essay Contest Winner Used A.I. Should She Return the $1,000 Award?</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2025/09/10/magazine/essay-contest-ai-ethics.html</link><description>What happened should be taken as a wake-up call, rather than a crime scene.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Is It Cutesy or Abominable to Make Up Random Words?</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/interactive/2025/09/12/magazine/word-shortening-hodgman-quiz.html</link><description>A ruling on a dispute over shortening “groceries” to “grosh.”</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>How the Trump Administration Is Dismantling America’s Cancer-Research System</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2025/09/14/magazine/trump-administration-cancer.html</link><description>Here are the takeaways from The New York Times Times Magazine article on how the cancer-research system, which has helped save millions of lives, is under threat in one of its most productive moments.</description><pubDate>Sun, 14 Sep 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Trump Is Shutting Down the War On Cancer</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2025/09/14/magazine/cancer-research-grants-funds-trump.html</link><description>America’s cancer research system, which has helped save millions of lives, is under threat in one of its most productive moments.</description><pubDate>Sun, 14 Sep 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Late-Night TV Is Fading. There’s One Part You May Come to Miss.</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2025/09/16/magazine/late-night-tv.html</link><description>Most of what late-night talk shows offer has been supplanted by the internet — except for the role of the wry, dispassionate host.</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>It Isn’t Just the U.S. The Whole World Has Soured on Climate Politics.</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2025/09/16/magazine/climate-politics-us-world-paris-agreement.html</link><description>How do we think about the climate future, now that the era marked by the Paris Agreement has so utterly disappeared?</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>