<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>NYT — Magazine</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/international/section/magazine</link><description>Latest stories from NYT Magazine</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 12:53:16 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>How ‘Affordability’ Became a New Magic Word for Politicians</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2025/12/18/magazine/affordability-economy.html</link><description>A rallying cry for Democrats taps into frustration over the inaccessibility of a modestly nice American existence — even for those with a decent income.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Can You Let Your Dog Run Off-Leash Wherever You Want?</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/interactive/2025/12/19/magazine/off-leash-dogs-hodgman-quiz.html</link><description>A ruling on a dispute over the use of shared spaces.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Raja Shehadeh Believes Israelis and Palestinians Can Still Find Peace</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2025/12/20/magazine/raja-shehadeh-interview.html</link><description>The writer and lawyer has been documenting the occupation for decades. Somehow, he maintains hope.</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>The ‘Masculinity Crisis’ Is Real. This Forgotten Book Explains Why.</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2025/12/23/magazine/masculinity-crisis-norah-vincent.html</link><description>Why do men find it so hard to connect with other people, and their own emotions?</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Shelters Won’t Let My Mother Adopt a Dog. Can I Pretend It’s for Me?</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2025/12/24/magazine/dog-adoption-ethics.html</link><description>Which is the more ethical course: honoring the system’s ageist rules, or bending those rules in service of compassion?</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>A Rupture Over Israel Is Tearing MAGA Apart</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2025/12/30/magazine/maga-israel-antisemitism-tucker-carlson.html</link><description>For 40 years, Christian Zionism was a powerful force in American politics. A new generation on the right is taking cues from elsewhere.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>In Ukraine, a New Arsenal of Killer A.I. Drones Is Being Born</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2025/12/31/magazine/ukraine-ai-drones-war-russia.html</link><description>As the war grinds on, sophisticated Russian defenses have pushed Ukraine to develop a frightening new weapon: semiautonomous killing machines.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Four Takeaways From the New York Times Profile of Marjorie Taylor Greene</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2025/12/29/magazine/marjorie-taylor-greene-interview-takeaways.html</link><description>The congresswoman discussed her break with President Trump and her journey from MAGA zealot to political isolation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>There’s Something Missing in Films About Jewish Cultural Figures</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2025/12/31/magazine/jewish-people-movies-neil-diamond.html</link><description>Why do films relating to Neil Diamond, Bob Dylan and Robert Oppenheimer barely mention their Jewishness?</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>To Feel at Home in a New Place, It Helps to Think Like a Snail</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2025/12/30/magazine/moving-abroad-snails.html</link><description>When I moved abroad, I found the slimy mollusks everywhere. Then they taught me how to adapt.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>‘I Was Just So Naïve’: Inside Marjorie Taylor Greene’s Break With Trump</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2025/12/29/magazine/marjorie-taylor-greene-trump-maga-split.html</link><description>How the Georgia congresswoman went from the president’s loudest cheerleader to his loudest Republican critic.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>