<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>Semafor — Media</title><link>https://www.semafor.com/vertical/media</link><description>Latest media stories from Semafor</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 08:28:07 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>Audiobook growth contrasts with print</title><link>https://www.semafor.com/article/12/30/2025/audiobook-growth-contrasts-with-print</link><description>Overall, sales of audio versions of books grew 1% in the year through October after rising more than 20% in 2024.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Kevin O’Leary on playing the villain and turning attention into power</title><link>https://www.semafor.com/article/01/02/2026/kevin-oleary-mixed-signals</link><description>Shark Tank’s Kevin O’Leary joins Mixed Signals to talk about his buzzy turn as a ruthless tycoon in Marty Supreme — and how it felt playing a fictionalized version of himself.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>New anchor Dokoupil sets the tone for ‘CBS Evening News’</title><link>https://www.semafor.com/article/01/04/2026/new-anchor-sets-the-tone-for-cbs-evening-news</link><description>In his opening monologue, Tony Dokoupil lamented that his colleagues in the news business had leaned too much into the perspectives of subject matter experts.</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Ryan Lizza on Olivia Nuzzi, RFK Jr., and the Substack-ification of a scandal</title><link>https://www.semafor.com/article/01/09/2026/ryan-lizza-mixed-signals</link><description>The media veteran joins Mixed Signals for a raw, sprawling conversation about why he chose to publish an eight-part (and counting) Substack series responding to the most personal and public crisis of his career.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>The business of a viral Substack scandal isn’t as good as you think, Ryan Lizza says</title><link>https://www.semafor.com/article/01/09/2026/ryan-lizza-olivia-nuzzi-substack-profits</link><description>“On the money part, not enough,” Lizza said on Semafor’s “Mixed Signals” podcast when asked about how much money he made off of the 25,000-word series.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Pro-Trump group to air Super Bowl ad touting Trump Accounts</title><link>https://www.semafor.com/article/01/11/2026/pro-trump-group-to-air-super-bowl-ad-touting-trump-accounts</link><description>It’s the latest move by a president and administration that have fully embraced professional sports as a prime venue to deliver their message.</description><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Blackstone invests $100M in elite marketing tech firm</title><link>https://www.semafor.com/article/01/11/2026/blackstone-invests-100m-in-elite-marketing-tech-firm</link><description>Applecart has a leading place in an emerging but discreet cohort of companies and organizations aimed at reaching key figures in industry and government.</description><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Politico announces layoffs, new product</title><link>https://www.semafor.com/article/01/14/2026/politico-announces-layoffs-and-a-new-product</link><description>The publication will cut about 3% of its 750-strong global staff.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Undersecretary Sarah Rogers on free speech, Europe’s tech crackdown, and the internet she misses</title><link>https://www.semafor.com/article/01/16/2026/mixed-signals-sarah-rogers</link><description>The State Department’s undersecretary for public diplomacy joins Mixed Signals for a wide-ranging conversation about free speech, tech regulation, and why she’s been rattling the patience of some European governments.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Die Welt editor departed amid internal inquiry</title><link>https://www.semafor.com/article/01/18/2026/die-welt-editor-departed-amid-internal-inquiry</link><description>The editor of Germany’s Die Welt had been the subject of internal scrutiny in recent days by the newspaper’s parent company.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Streaming giants push filmmakers to adapt to ‘double screening’</title><link>https://www.semafor.com/article/01/20/2026/streaming-giants-push-filmmakers-to-adapt-to-double-screening</link><description>Viewers are increasingly watching films and TV while also looking at their smartphones.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Freakonomics’ Stephen Dubner on why long-form podcasting isn’t dead yet</title><link>https://www.semafor.com/article/01/23/2026/freakanomics-stephen-dubner-mixed-signals</link><description>Stephen Dubner has spent 20 years proving that things aren’t what they seem—and now he’s not so sure that’s always true.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>“We’re not trying to recreate social media”: How Minnesota’s Star Tribune navigates a local crisis</title><link>https://www.semafor.com/article/01/24/2026/the-power-of-video-is-real-but-limited-how-minnesotas-star-tribune-navigates-a-local-crisis</link><description>The publication tries to offer a sober alternative to a social media swarm as a deadly shooting deepens the crisis in Minneapolis.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Rumors of staffing cuts spook Washington Post newsroom</title><link>https://www.semafor.com/article/01/25/2026/rumors-of-staffing-cuts-spook-washington-post-newsroom</link><description>Feared potential targets for cuts include the sports and international desks.</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Washington Post’s White House team tries to avert layoffs in letter to Bezos</title><link>https://www.semafor.com/article/01/29/2026/washington-posts-white-house-team-tries-to-avert-layoffs-in-letter-to-bezos</link><description>The effort from the Post’s White House reporters comes as staffers are scrambling to preserve their jobs ahead of impending layoffs.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>The exec behind Canada’s surprise hit ‘Heated Rivalry’ on the secret to its success</title><link>https://www.semafor.com/article/01/30/2026/the-exec-behind-canadas-surprise-hit-heated-rivalry-on-the-secret-to-its-success</link><description>Sean Cohan gets into the Canadian-ness of it all on the “Mixed Signals” podcast.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>It’s Rupe vs. the Quiff! In California’s new tabloid war, everybody wins</title><link>https://www.semafor.com/article/02/01/2026/its-rupe-vs-the-quiff-in-californias-new-tabloid-war-everybody-wins</link><description>The California Post is betting its buzzy launch on a war with Gov. Gavin Newsom.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Podcast brand Kaleidoscope staffs up</title><link>https://www.semafor.com/article/02/01/2026/podcast-brand-kaleidoscope-staffs-up</link><description>The company is filling out its executive ranks as it hopes to break further into video.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>