<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>Washington Post — Investigations</title><link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/national/investigations/</link><description>Latest investigations from Washington Post</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 06:45:41 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>Exclusive</title><link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/investigations/2025/12/30/anglican-church-leader-dobbs-investigations/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>He was attacked on Jan. 6. Can he make sense of it for the kids he teaches?Nathan Tate was a D.C. police officer defending the U.S. Capitol on January 6. Now he’s trying to find the lesson in it.</title><link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/investigations/2026/01/06/capitol-jan6-riot-attack-teacher/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Five years after Jan. 6, officers describe the toll of defending the CapitolIn his first day in office, Trump pardoned nearly 1,600 people in the Jan. 6th Capitol riot. The country has moved on, but for some the day still looms large.</title><link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/investigations/2026/01/06/capitol-jan6-riot-police-attack/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Video shows ICE agent in Minneapolis fired at driver as vehicle veered past himAn analysis of video footage raises questions about claims by President Donald Trump and Homeland Security Secretary Kristi L. Noem about the fatal shooting in Minneapolis.</title><link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/investigations/2026/01/08/video-ice-shooting-minneapolis/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>The ICE agent’s cellphone video: Five key momentsCellphone footage shows what happened in the moments before and after an ICE agent Jonathan Ross fatally shot Renée Good in Minneapolis.</title><link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/investigations/2026/01/09/moments-before-ice-shooting-minneapolis/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>11 tankers under U.S. sanctions defy blockade in Venezuela, satellite imagery indicatesOne ship was seized Friday in the Caribbean, and others were spotted steaming hundreds of miles into the Atlantic.</title><link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/investigations/2026/01/10/venezuela-oil-tankers-us-blockade/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Videos show security forces firing into crowds in at least six cities across IranA Washington Post review of videos from Iran posted online of recent protests illustrates how widely violence has spread.</title><link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/investigations/2026/01/14/iran-protests-videos-government-crackdown/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Federal agent secured gun from Minn. man before fatal shooting, videos showA Washington Post analysis of videos sheds light on the encounter that left 37-year-old Alex Pretti dead.</title><link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/investigations/2026/01/25/minneapolis-shooting-video-gun/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Iranian forces massacred protesters fleeing burning market, witnesses sayA rare detailed account of Iran’s crackdown, produced by The Post, reveals the brutality used by security forces in one of many such cities rocked by violence.</title><link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/investigations/2026/01/25/iran-rasht-protests-regime-crackdown/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>What video shows about Don Lemon’s activities at the church protestA Post review of videos from the protest at Minnesota’s Cities Church offers a detailed look at the events that led to the arrest of the former CNN anchor.</title><link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/investigations/2026/01/23/don-lemon-minneapolis/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>ICE buys warehouses for mass detention network, rattling localsICE officials have quietly begun notifying warehouse owners and local officials of their interest in specific properties, prompting efforts to block the projects.</title><link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/investigations/2026/01/30/ice-warehouse-detention-dhs-immigration/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Exclusive</title><link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/investigations/2026/02/03/homeland-security-administrative-subpoena/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Those seeking to sue ICE for injuries or damage face an uphill battleScores of claims are expected to arise out of the Trump administration’s crackdown on illegal immigration. Experts say suing the government will be tough.</title><link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/investigations/2026/02/06/ice-legal-claims-cost-lawsuits/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>