<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>The New Yorker — Reporting</title><link>https://www.newyorker.com/magazine/reporting</link><description>Latest reporting from The New Yorker</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 07:19:49 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>Patrick Radden Keefe on Truman Capote’s “In Cold Blood”</title><link>https://www.newyorker.com/magazine/takes/patrick-radden-keefe-on-truman-capotes-in-cold-blood</link><description>Capote’s journalistic transgressions were serious, but there is no denying the awesome influence of his work.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 07:19:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Denmark Is Sick of Being Bullied by Trump</title><link>https://www.newyorker.com/magazine/2026/01/19/denmark-is-sick-of-being-bullied-by-trump</link><description>The U.S., once Denmark’s closest ally, is threatening to steal Greenland and attacking the country’s wind-power industry. Is this a permanent breakup?</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 07:19:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>The Backcountry Rescue Squad at America’s Busiest National Park</title><link>https://www.newyorker.com/magazine/2026/01/19/the-backcountry-rescue-squad-at-americas-busiest-national-park</link><description>In the Great Smoky Mountains, an auxiliary team of élite outdoorsmen answers the call when park-goers’ hikes, climbs, and rafting adventures go wrong.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 07:19:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>How Marco Rubio Went from “Little Marco” to Trump’s Foreign-Policy Enabler</title><link>https://www.newyorker.com/magazine/2026/01/19/marco-rubio-profile</link><description>As Secretary of State, the President’s onetime foe now offers him lavish displays of public praise—and will execute his agenda in Venezuela and around the globe.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 07:19:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>How WhatsApp Took Over the Global Conversation</title><link>https://www.newyorker.com/magazine/2026/01/19/how-whatsapp-took-over-the-global-conversation</link><description>The platform has become a core technology around the world, relied on by governments and extended families alike. What are we all doing there?</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 07:19:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>The Lights Are Still On in Venezuela</title><link>https://www.newyorker.com/magazine/2026/01/26/the-lights-are-still-on-in-venezuela</link><description>After the ouster of President Nicolás Maduro, some residents fear that one unelected despot has been swapped for another.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 07:19:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Vinson Cunningham on Barry Blitt’s Obama “Fist Bump” Cover</title><link>https://www.newyorker.com/magazine/takes/vinson-cunningham-on-barry-blitts-obama-fist-bump-cover</link><description>Here’s one big risk a public satirist of racism takes: by displaying tropes and crude imagery, he reveals just how well he knows and can deploy them himself.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 07:19:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Inside Bari Weiss’s Hostile Takeover of CBS News</title><link>https://www.newyorker.com/magazine/2026/01/26/inside-bari-weisss-hostile-takeover-of-cbs-news</link><description>The network’s new editor-in-chief has championed a press free from élite bias, while aligning herself with a billionaire class more willing than ever to indulge Donald Trump.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 07:19:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>The Congresswoman Criminalized for Visiting ICE Detainees</title><link>https://www.newyorker.com/magazine/2026/01/26/lamonica-mciver-congress-ice-jail-visit-felony-charges</link><description>LaMonica McIver went to tour an immigration jail in her New Jersey district. Now she faces seventeen years in prison.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 07:19:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>The Ice Curtain</title><link>https://www.newyorker.com/magazine/2026/01/19/the-ice-curtain</link><description>Since Putin invaded Ukraine, the short distance between Nome, Alaska, and Russia seems wider than ever.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 07:19:49 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>