<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>NYT — Magazine</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/international/section/magazine</link><description>Latest stories from NYT Magazine</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 18:40:22 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>The ‘Masculinity Crisis’ Is Real. This Forgotten Book Explains Why.</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2025/12/23/magazine/masculinity-crisis-norah-vincent.html</link><description>Why do men find it so hard to connect with other people, and their own emotions?</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Shelters Won’t Let My Mother Adopt a Dog. Can I Pretend It’s for Me?</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2025/12/24/magazine/dog-adoption-ethics.html</link><description>Which is the more ethical course: honoring the system’s ageist rules, or bending those rules in service of compassion?</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>What It’s Like When Your Wife Goes on Testosterone</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2025/12/26/magazine/what-its-like-when-your-wife-goes-on-testosterone.html</link><description>She went on testosterone to help with her menopausal symptoms. The effects had unexpected consequences for their marriage.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>He Was a Supreme Court Lawyer. Then His Double Life Caught Up With Him.</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2025/12/28/magazine/thomas-goldstein-supreme-court-gambling.html</link><description>Thomas Goldstein was a superstar in the legal world. He was also a secret high-stakes gambler, whose wild 10-year run may now land him in prison.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Four Takeaways From the New York Times Profile of Marjorie Taylor Greene</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2025/12/29/magazine/marjorie-taylor-greene-interview-takeaways.html</link><description>The congresswoman discussed her break with President Trump and her journey from MAGA zealot to political isolation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>To Feel at Home in a New Place, It Helps to Think Like a Snail</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2025/12/30/magazine/moving-abroad-snails.html</link><description>When I moved abroad, I found the slimy mollusks everywhere. Then they taught me how to adapt.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Someone Made Anonymous Accusations About My Friend. What Should I Do?</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2026/01/03/magazine/anonymous-accusations-friend-ethics.html</link><description>Normally I would listen to my gut, but even my gut is stumped.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>On ‘The Pitt,’ E.R. Doctors Try to Fix This Broken World</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2026/01/04/magazine/the-pitt-season-2-noah-wyle.html</link><description>Noah Wyle and his castmates turned one harrowing day at an E.R. into an unforgettable season of television. Can they do it again?</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Could Viral Protest Videos Create a Backlash Against ‘Less Lethal’ Weapons?</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2026/01/07/magazine/anti-ice-protest-videos-less-lethal-weapons.html</link><description>They were developed during the civil rights movement to reduce harm, but their rampant use during anti-ICE protests has led to a new kind of violence.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Do I Have to Tell My New Boyfriend About My Past Infidelity?</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2026/01/07/magazine/past-infidelity-ethics.html</link><description>He knows I started seeing someone as my marriage was deteriorating, but I have not admitted the full truth.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>In Ukraine, a New Arsenal of Killer A.I. Drones Is Being Born</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2025/12/31/magazine/ukraine-ai-drones-war-russia.html</link><description>As the war grinds on, sophisticated Russian defenses have pushed Ukraine to develop a frightening new weapon: semiautonomous killing machines.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>