<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>Semafor — Media</title><link>https://www.semafor.com/vertical/media</link><description>Latest media stories from Semafor</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 18:35:08 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>Trump to sit with CBS News in first interview after lawsuit</title><link>https://www.semafor.com/article/10/31/2025/trump-to-sit-with-cbs-news-in-first-interview-after-lawsuit</link><description>The US president is set to sit down with CBS anchor Norah O’Donnell on Friday afternoon, Semafor has learned.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>The new Vanity Fair’s one rule: Leave the princesses alone!</title><link>https://www.semafor.com/article/11/02/2025/the-new-vanity-fairs-one-rule-leave-the-princesses-alone</link><description>Vanity Fair is trying to offer meaningful journalism that reveals inner workings of power — while also convincing the powerful to pose for its covers and attend its Hollywood events.</description><pubDate>Sun, 02 Nov 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Can anyone stop Tucker Carlson?</title><link>https://www.semafor.com/article/11/03/2025/carlson-fuentes-and-the-right-wing-rift-over-antisemitism</link><description>The uproar over his interview with Nick Fuentes only seemed to boost his profile.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Wikipedia founder says ‘Gaza genocide’ page lacked neutrality</title><link>https://www.semafor.com/article/11/04/2025/wikipedia-founder-says-its-gaza-genocide-page-lacked-neutrality</link><description>The publicly editable nature of Wikipedia makes it a battleground, with entires often becoming viewed as established fact.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Michael Wolff crowdfunds war chest to pursue Melania Trump</title><link>https://www.semafor.com/article/11/06/2025/michael-wolff-crowdfunds-war-chest-to-pursue-melania-trump</link><description>The first lady had threatened Wolff with a defamation case over comments he made on his podcast linking her to Jeffrey Epstein.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Condé Nast abruptly fires 4 staffers after HR confrontation</title><link>https://www.semafor.com/article/11/06/2025/cond-nast-abruptly-fires-4-staffers-after-hr-confrontation</link><description>The firings were an unsubtle message to its employee union that the publisher was taking a harder line in its dealings with employees.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Zaslav meets with Comcast executives as bidding war ramps up</title><link>https://www.semafor.com/article/11/09/2025/warner-bros-discoverys-zaslav-meets-with-comcast-executives-as-bidding-war-ramps-up</link><description>Comcast may feel there is still a path forward for a deal.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Axel Springer’s CEO — and biggest star — is chasing his next deal</title><link>https://www.semafor.com/article/11/09/2025/axel-springers-ceo-and-biggest-star-is-chasing-his-next-deal</link><description>Mathias Döpfner is emerging as a new-school mogul: ubiquitously public, sitting on a pile of cash, and on the hunt for more deals.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>BBC director general quits over Trump reporting</title><link>https://www.semafor.com/article/11/10/2025/bbc-director-general-quits-over-trump-reporting</link><description>He resigned over a report suggesting the broadcaster had misleadingly edited a speech by US President Donald Trump.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Comcast, Paramount, Netflix near bids for Warner Bros. Discovery</title><link>https://www.semafor.com/article/11/13/2025/comcast-paramount-netflix-near-bids-for-warner-bros-discovery</link><description>A frenetic pursuit for the last big chunk of media assets is entering its next stage.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>An unpublished profile raises questions about Epstein — and journalism</title><link>https://www.semafor.com/article/11/16/2025/in-an-unpublished-column-questions-about-epstein-and-about-journalism</link><description>Buried deep in the House Oversight Committee’s recent release of emails from Jeffrey Epstein’s inbox is an 8,684-word profile by the reporter Michael Wolff.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>The old MSNBC relaunches into a new media world</title><link>https://www.semafor.com/article/11/16/2025/the-old-msnbc-relaunches-into-a-new-media-world</link><description>The network, now called MS NOW, is in the midst of its biggest gamble since it launched in 1996.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Vox to partner with Patreon for new paywalled shows</title><link>https://www.semafor.com/article/11/16/2025/vox-to-partner-with-patreon-for-new-subscriber-only-shows</link><description>Vox said it hopes to supplement its shows with live newsroom conversations and community features such as chats.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Derek Thompson on why everything is becoming television, and whether democracy can survive it</title><link>https://www.semafor.com/article/11/14/2025/derek-thompson-mixed-signals</link><description>Derek Thompson explores why endless video feeds are commanding attention like never before, his book Abundance, his shift from The Atlantic, and the leap to independent work.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Can the Supreme Court keep its secrets? With Jodi Kantor of the New York Times</title><link>https://www.semafor.com/article/11/21/2025/supreme-court-secrets-jodi-kantor-new-york-times</link><description>New York Times investigative reporter Jodi Kantor joins Mixed Signals to explain how she’s revealed the secrets of internal deliberations behind the ceremony and black robes of the US Supreme Court.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CNN drops out of Apple News feed, for now</title><link>https://www.semafor.com/article/11/23/2025/cnn-drops-out-of-apple-news-feed</link><description>The two companies are continuing to discuss a new deal that would restore CNN’s stories to Apple News.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>How Trump is trying to remake American culture — starting with his favorite buddy-cop franchise</title><link>https://www.semafor.com/article/11/23/2025/how-trump-is-trying-to-remake-american-culture-starting-with-rush-hour</link><description>The president is offering some creative input on potential upcoming projects.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>UK’s The Telegraph to be taken over by rival Daily Mail</title><link>https://www.semafor.com/article/11/24/2025/uks-the-telegraph-to-be-taken-over-by-rival-daily-mail</link><description>The outlet has been for sale since its previous owners ran up unsupportable debts and were removed in 2023.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>