<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>Semafor — Media</title><link>https://www.semafor.com/vertical/media</link><description>Latest media stories from Semafor</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2025 02:08:32 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>The old MSNBC relaunches into a new media world</title><link>https://www.semafor.com/article/11/16/2025/the-old-msnbc-relaunches-into-a-new-media-world</link><description>The network, now called MS NOW, is in the midst of its biggest gamble since it launched in 1996.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Vox to partner with Patreon for new paywalled shows</title><link>https://www.semafor.com/article/11/16/2025/vox-to-partner-with-patreon-for-new-subscriber-only-shows</link><description>Vox said it hopes to supplement its shows with live newsroom conversations and community features such as chats.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Derek Thompson on why everything is becoming television, and whether democracy can survive it</title><link>https://www.semafor.com/article/11/14/2025/derek-thompson-mixed-signals</link><description>Derek Thompson explores why endless video feeds are commanding attention like never before, his book Abundance, his shift from The Atlantic, and the leap to independent work.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Can the Supreme Court keep its secrets? With Jodi Kantor of the New York Times</title><link>https://www.semafor.com/article/11/21/2025/supreme-court-secrets-jodi-kantor-new-york-times</link><description>New York Times investigative reporter Jodi Kantor joins Mixed Signals to explain how she’s revealed the secrets of internal deliberations behind the ceremony and black robes of the US Supreme Court.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CNN drops out of Apple News feed, for now</title><link>https://www.semafor.com/article/11/23/2025/cnn-drops-out-of-apple-news-feed</link><description>The two companies are continuing to discuss a new deal that would restore CNN’s stories to Apple News.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>How Trump is trying to remake American culture — starting with his favorite buddy-cop franchise</title><link>https://www.semafor.com/article/11/23/2025/how-trump-is-trying-to-remake-american-culture-starting-with-rush-hour</link><description>The president is offering some creative input on potential upcoming projects.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>UK’s The Telegraph to be taken over by rival Daily Mail</title><link>https://www.semafor.com/article/11/24/2025/uks-the-telegraph-to-be-taken-over-by-rival-daily-mail</link><description>The outlet has been for sale since its previous owners ran up unsupportable debts and were removed in 2023.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Vanity Fair expected to let Olivia Nuzzi’s contract lapse, insiders say</title><link>https://www.semafor.com/article/11/30/2025/vanity-fairs-editors-mull-what-to-do-about-nuzzi</link><description>Just weeks after Vanity Fair published an excerpt of Olivia Nuzzi’s book, it’s increasingly unlikely she’ll be a fixture on its print masthead.</description><pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Staff cuts and strategy squabbles split Atlas Obscura leadership</title><link>https://www.semafor.com/article/12/04/2025/staff-cuts-and-strategy-squabbles-split-atlas-obscura-leadership</link><description>The relationship between the company’s founders and some of its investors appears to have soured.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CNN staffers, bracing for Paramount takeover, are relieved by Netflix deal</title><link>https://www.semafor.com/article/12/07/2025/cnn-staffers-bracing-for-paramount-takeover-are-relieved-by-netflix-deal</link><description>As federal regulators weigh Netflix’s acquisition of Warner Bros. Discovery’s studio and streaming business, WBD will continue spinning off its cable assets.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>AI critics funded AI coverage at top newsrooms</title><link>https://www.semafor.com/article/12/07/2025/ai-critics-funded-ai-coverage-at-top-newsrooms</link><description>A behind-the-scenes media war over coverage of AI reflects a deep split inside the tech community.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>In mad dash to stop Netflix-WBD deal, Paramount has ‘no juice’</title><link>https://www.semafor.com/article/12/07/2025/in-mad-dash-to-stop-netflix-wbd-deal-paramount-has-no-juice</link><description>Seemingly everyone hates that Netflix won out in the bidding war for Warner Bros. Discovery, but the Ellisons couldn’t stop it.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Paramount’s Mideast financing doomed Warner Bros. Discovery auction bid</title><link>https://www.semafor.com/article/12/08/2025/paramounts-mideast-financing-doomed-warner-bros-discovery-auction-bid</link><description>WBD’s board grew uneasy with how complicated Paramount’s offer became.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Investors warm to Paramount’s bid for Warner Bros.</title><link>https://www.semafor.com/article/12/09/2025/investors-warm-to-paramounts-bid-for-warner-brothers</link><description>David Ellison and his team impressed Warner Bros. investors with their pitch — and their price tag.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Senator has ‘grave doubts’ about Netflix-WBD deal</title><link>https://www.semafor.com/article/12/09/2025/senator-has-grave-doubts-about-netflix-wbd-deal</link><description>Sen. Mike Lee, who sits on the Senate Judiciary Committee, said he wouldn’t be surprised if it gets “thwarted.”</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Democrats warn their party may try to unravel any Paramount-Warner Bros. Discovery deal</title><link>https://www.semafor.com/article/12/10/2025/democrats-warn-their-party-may-try-to-unravel-any-paramount-warner-bros-discovery-deal</link><description>A new letter from Reps. Sam Liccardo, D-Calif., and Ayanna Pressley, D-Mass., also raised concerns about foreign investors’ involvement.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Washington Post’s AI-generated podcasts rife with errors, fictional quotes</title><link>https://www.semafor.com/article/12/11/2025/washington-posts-ai-generated-podcasts-rife-with-errors-fictional-quotes</link><description>Errors in the Post’s new AI-generated podcasts have frustrated the paper’s journalists.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Opposition to Netflix-Warner deal grows in Washington</title><link>https://www.semafor.com/article/12/12/2025/opposition-to-netflix-paramount-deal-grows-in-washington</link><description>Sen. Tim Scott, a Republican with close ties to the White House, joined the mounting opposition in Washington to Netflix’s takeover of Warner Bros.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>